<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tasks on Business Implementation Learning Diary</title>
    <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tasks on Business Implementation Learning Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Task</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task1/</guid>
      <description>About a good leader A good team manager that end up to be a leader is one of the most important in an enterprise a good leadership can help a company and team thrive.
A good leader should have characteristics as follow:
 He/She should be self-aware Should have Self-direction and should find the path and next step for themself and their team. Should have vision Should have emotionally stable and think long term development  I worked in different jobs and positions during time and had to work with differernt types of managers and leaders a good leader that help to improve the company and team make the working environment good and stable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Task</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task2/</guid>
      <description>Google Marketing I googled &amp;ldquo;mobile application development&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;computer security service&amp;rdquo; and in the results we can see several companies shows up with the &amp;ldquo;Ad&amp;rdquo; tag that advertised their website to show as first results in google search.
We can name Ciklum, Oracle, iflexion, Tieto that payed for special position but we can say almost all good enterprises that are showing up in first few pages on google did some google marketing and search engine optimization (SEO)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Task</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task3/</guid>
      <description>Polar Bear Pitching 2018 It&amp;rsquo;s an international event happening every year in Oulu focusing on new businesses with the presence of investors, the idea is that the owners pitch their idea when they are standing in an ice hole they have time as long as they can keep standing in the ice hole and talk about their business.
It is a very fun and cool event and eveyone get to meet new people with different ideas in a nice environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forth Task</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task4/</guid>
      <description>Visiting Business Kitchen As they defined themselves in business kitchen website they are Oulu universities’ entrepreneurship hub, a community and co-working space to boost action and discover new opportunities in business and in life.
Last year they were placed in city center but this year they moved to OAMK Kotkantie campus.
They hold different kind of events connecting people and businesses together and helping them grows and learn events for kickstarting and for startups like startup weekend Avanto and Demola, polar bear pitching and etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fifth Task</title>
      <link>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 15:07:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://shajadi.com/bi/tasks/task5/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Reports 1. 24 / 7 Online Food They are a kitchen only food delivery business that want to make it cheap and accessible for people to order and receive their food online and fast.
For them getting pass the regulation and needed licenses as a food business can be biggest challenge also managing the legislation is challenge too.
2. Ticketr They want to resolve the problems with ordinary online ticket selling companies that is kind of a monopoly by ticketmaster the problems are holding high prices for tickets and also overselling the tickets in blackmarket and all the scams around it, they charge 2% of ticket cost and also 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>